警察学校Ⅳ
全民警察
接着来 哥们
Take it, brother.
打倒你!
Let me break you.
嗨 这真可怕!
Man, that was funky.
- 前面注意! - 噢 我猜会议已经开始了
- Fore! - Well, I guess the meeting's started.
- 您好 长官! - 马霍尼! 琼斯!
- Howdy, sir? - Mahoney! Jones!
谢谢 斯威特查克
Thank you, Sweetchuck.
关于我的新计划我得到了极棒极棒的消息
I've had the most wonderful newsabout my new program.
- 长官 是什么新计划? - 全市公民作为警察巡逻计划
- What new program is that, sir? - My citizens on patrol.
简单点 我叫它"全民警察"
I call it C.O.P. for short.
不错的警察团体 你们说呢?
Has a nice policey ring to it,don't you think?
什么是"全民警察" 长官?
What is C.O.P., sir?
警察工作最让人感到灰心丧气的是什么?
What is the most frustrating thingabout police work?
- 不给配备手榴弹 - 隔离室 长官
- Not being able to carry hand grenades. - Separate locker rooms, sir.
令人作呕的蓝制服
Icky blue uniforms.
我一直认为最让人泄气的事情是…
I always thoughtthat the most frustrating thing was that...
我们不能立刻赶到所有的犯罪现场去解决所有的犯罪
we couldn't be everywhere at onceto solve every crime.
所以最终公众会把我们当作敌人
So the public ends upthinking of us as enemies.
如果他们能把我们所有人都看作朋友该有多好啊!
Wouldn't it be wonderfulif we could all be friends?
啊 马霍尼警官 请进来
Officer Mahoney, please come in.
来点柠檬水 我喜欢喝柠檬水
Have some lemonade. I love lemonade.
- 别太酸了 别… - …太甜了 嗯 不错
- Not too tart, not - - - Too sweet, just good.
所以"全民警察"是一项社会行动计划 长官
So C.O.P. isa community action program, sir.
- 就象邻里监督组织? - 更强! 更棒!
- Like Neighborhood Watch? - More. Much more!
我们向公众显示我们的关心
We show the community that we care.
我们训练志愿者们如何进行犯罪侦查如何进行急救 还有、还有…
We train volunteers in crime detection,in first - aid and....
- 还有这是个不错的主意 长官 - 但我们需要公众的支持
- And it's a great idea, sir. - But we need citizen support.
周边的犯罪活动会让您得到他们的支持的
With all this neighborhood crime,I'm sure you'll get it.
- 前面注意! - 没错 如果我们…
- Fore! - Right. What if we were to....
如果什么?
What was that?
我相信斯威特查克兄弟想建议…
I believe brother Sweetchuckis suggesting...
我们在我们附近招募新兵
we recruit in our old neighborhood.
好主意! 我们有市长的全力支持…
Excellent. We have the full supportof the Mayor...
最棒的是 州长希望我下月…
and best of all, the Governor of the statewants me to unveil the program...
在英国举行的国际警察大会的最后…
at the end ofthe International Police Seminar...
把这一计划公诸于众
next month in England.
在我参会的时候…
While I attend the seminar...
你们 我的好朋友们…
you, my good friends...
将把"全民警察"计划付诸实施
will put C.O.P. into action.
这将改善全世界的警民关系
It will change community relationsall around the world.
拉萨方法
The Lassard Method.
听起来不错 是吧?
It rolls nicely off the tongue,don't you think?
嗨 我错过了什么?
Hi! What did I miss?
嗨
Hi.
哈里斯上尉 赫斯特委员来了
Capt. Harris,Police Commissioner Hurst is here.
您想见他吗?
You want to see him?
不 把他赶走
No. Send him packing.
是 长官!
Yes, sir.
- 学监! - 什么事 长官?
- Proctor! - Yes, sir?
立即把他请进来
Send the Commissioner in immediately.
- 我想您说要把他赶走 - 马上!
- I thought you said to send him packing. - Immediately!
是 长官!
Yes, sir.
没用的东西
Nincompoop.
委员
Commissioner.
- 你有问题 哈里斯上尉? - 是的 长官
- You have a problem, Capt. Harris? - Yes, sir.
委员先生 我对这张从拉萨那里来的传单非常关心…
Commissioner, I am extremely concernedwith this memorandum from Lassard...
关于他的"全民警察"计划
about his C.O.P. program.
让市民去做警察工作? 多蠢的想法
Citizens doing police work?An asinine idea.
如果这被通过 警察的工作、薪水都将没有保证
If this goes through, no policeman's job,no policeman's paycheck, will be safe.
你是不是不想干了?
Are you through, Captain?
州长认为这个计划非常的有创意
The Governor of this state thinksthat this program is absolutely brilliant.
如果他改变主意我就会同意你的看法
So until he changes his mind,that's what you and I think, too.
没意见吧?
Agreed?
- 没有 长官 - 很好
- Yes, sir. - Good.
您一开始很英明您真应该把他赶走
You were right.You should have sent him packing.
我才不在乎州长跟市长会怎么想
I don't give a damnwhat the Governor or the Mayor thinks.
拉萨的计划是个错误…
Lassard's program is a mistake...
任何同意他的想法都是错的
and anyone who thinks otherwiseis wrong.
完全错误
Pure and simple.
别碰它!
Don't touch those!
我看你再敢不经我允许就碰我的球!
Don't you ever touch my ballswithout asking!
请你离开这我会报警! 我是认真的
You're gonna have to leave.I'll call the police. I mean it.
行、行 我这就走 离开这
Okay, I'm going. I'm out of here.
等会儿 我就是警察
Wait a minute. I am the police.
- 不 你不是 - 我是 我来这想谈一下"全民警察"计划
- No, you're not. - That's me. I'm here to speak about C.O.P.
抱歉 我没有…没有警服…
I'm sorry. I didn't....Without the uniform on - -
便装会使公民感觉更舒服
Regular human clothesmake people more comfortable.
嗨 女士们 我们来作诗吧!
Hi, ladies. Let's do some poetry!
我今晚得去丈人家吃晚饭
I got to go to my in - laws'for dinner tonight.
你想来吗?
You want to come?
高塔警官 我来参加"全民警察"计划
Officer Hightower,I'm here to join the new C.O.P. Program.
我认识你吗?
Do I know you?
认识 你曾让我坐在你的腿上玩
Yeah, you used tobounce me on your knee.
- 我有过吗? - 当然! 小汤米·康克林
- I did? - Yeah. Little Tommy Conklin.
- 但现在他们叫我大房子 - 汤米·康克林
- But now they call me House. - Tommy Conklin.
想起来了 欢迎你你可以到那边去登记
Sure. Welcome aboard.You can register right over there.
"惊恐的人儿啊紧闭了双唇
"Blind mouth that scare themselves
"除了一根牧羊杖啊
"know how to hold a sheep - hook
"他一无所有
"Or have learned aught else at least
"这就是忠诚的牧羊人生命的——归宿"
"that to the faithful Herdsmansart belongs! "
喔 真振奋人心!
That was exciting.
下面泽得警官将向我们宣布…
We have an Officer Zed,who's here to tell us...
一项新的警界计划请…
a little bit about a new police program.So won't you....
非、非常感谢
Thank you very much.
对不起我是一个很情绪化而且敏感的人…
I'm sorry.I'm an emotional, sensitive guy...
牧羊杖那部分把我的心完全撕碎了
and that part about the sheep - hookjust tore my heart right out.
我今天也准备了一首诗
I have my own poemthat I prepared for you today.
"吉恩、吉恩造了台机器…
"Gene, Gene made a machine...
"乔、乔使它转起…
"and Joe, Joe made it go.
"我放了个屁一个把它们全震烂的屁"
"l blew a fartand blew the whole damn thing apart."
他在说什么?
What is he saying?
我没把它写下来
I didn't write it.
好吧 我现在想告诉你们我来这里的目的…
Okay, I'd like to talk to youabout what we're here for...
把"全民警察"计划扔给你们
and that's for me to pitchthe new C.O.P. program to you.
可能你们中的一些人会对些感兴趣
Perhaps a few of you ladiesmight be interested in it.
于是酒吧招待问街头的手风琴师"嘿 你的猴子能唱歌剧吗? "
So the bartender asked the organ grinder,"Hey, does your monkey sing any opera?"
我说："不
And I said, "Nope.
"但如果你在我的脑袋上来一拳我会给你唱《美国傻瓜》"
"But if you hit me on the head,I'll sing Yankee Doodle. "
噢 一家人团聚在一起真棒!
It's so nice to have my familyall back together again.
- 爸爸 能把生菜给我递过来吗? - 当然 宝贝儿 给你
- Can you pass the lettuce, Pop? - Sure, honey. Here you go.
- 谢谢 爸爸 - 别客气 嘿 听着…
- Thanks, Pop. - You're welcome. Hey, listen...
我跟你们说我要参加"全民警察"计划了吗?
did I tell you I'm gonna jointhat Citizen On Patrol thing?
太棒了!我会为此地有你而骄傲的
That would be a great idea.I'd be proud to have you at the precinct.
我要再来点蔬菜 巴德
I'll take some more greens, Bud.
- 爸爸 - 什么事?
- Dad. - Yeah?
我觉得你不该去我们家已经有三个警察了
I don't think you should sign up.There are already three of us on the force.
- 会有人认为这是徇私不会的
- It's going to look like favoritism. - That's not it.
一点也不会你觉得我不再敏捷了 是吗?
That's not it at all. You just don't thinkI'm fast enough anymore, do you?
一点都不 对吧 塔克?
I don't think that's it, do you, Tack?
这跟敏捷没关系这才是
It has nothing to do with being fast.Now, that was fast.
嗯 不错
You know, that was fast.
但这招更酷
But that's hard.
过一下
Excuse me.
我觉得巴德伤了爸爸的感情
I think Bud hurt Pop's feelings.
噢 你们俩
Oh, you two.
噢 谁想要派?
Oh, well, who wants pie?
- 我只是想帮你一下 - 你伤了我的胳膊
- I was just trying to help. - You hurt my arm.
- 我会把剩下的发出去 嗨 - 嗨
- I'll hand the rest out. Hi. - Hi.
您对我们新的"全民警察"计划感兴趣吗?
Could I interest youin the new citizens program?
- 不 一点也不 - 噢 谢谢
- No, I don't think so. - No, thanks.
- 我们走楼梯 - 谢谢
- We'll take the stairs. - Thanks, just the same.
等一下!
Excuse me!
您对我们新的"全民警察"计划感兴趣吗?
Would you be interestedin the new citizens program?
- 是的 事实上 刚才我们没听清 - 很好 拿着
- Yes, in fact, we didn't hear you right. - Sure, here.
- 你们为什么不把这些传单分发一下? - 非常感谢 再见 先生
- Why don't you hand the rest of them out? - Thank you very much. Goodbye, sir.
- 阿尼 哪去? - 回家 我有一筐的事情要做
- Arnie, where are you going? - Home. I got a boatload of stuff to do.
我明天必须写完学期报告 还要考历史
I got a term paper due tomorrow,and a history test.
我要帮我爸爸打扫酒窖 晚上还要洗碗
I got to help my father clean the cellar,and I have to do the dishes tonight.
你什么事?
What are you doing?
- 我想去购物中心那边找那些家伙 - 走
- I'll get the guys and hang out at the mall. - Let's go.
我想我跟你们说过 我的地盘上不许玩滑板
I thought I told you guys,no skateboarding in my district.
我没有玩滑板 警官 我只是拿着滑板
This isn't skateboarding, Sergeant.This is carrying skateboards.
这才是玩滑板
This is skateboarding.
- 我们去那看看 - 慢走
- We got to check this out, you guys. - Take it easy.
再见
We'll see you later.
再见我想看会这些家伙表演
I'll see you later.I want to check out these guys.
好的 我一会儿回来
All right, I'll be back.
嘿 军士 看那
Hey, Sarge, look at that.
凯尔 那个玩滑板的小阿飞 盯住他
Kyle, that skateboard punk. Let's nail him.
嘿 你会让他们有的瞧的
Boy, you sure give them a hard time.
当然 很有趣吧?
Yeah. Fun, isn't it?
你不听话 是不是 凯尔?
You don't listen, do you, Kyle?
我在为哈里斯上尉买生日礼物
I was shoppingfor Capt. Harris' birthday present.
- 真的? - 真的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
换个地方买去
Shop somewhere else.
法官…
Your Honor....
您的 法官 抓住他! 拦住他!
Here, Judge. Stop him! Hold up!
对不起 对不起 让一下对不起 我的错
Excuse me, pardon me.Excuse me, my fault.
- 当心! - 站住! 拦住那个玩滑板的! 别让他走!
- Watch it! - Stop! Stop that skateboarder! Hold it!
我也能这样 头朝下
I can do that, that handstand stuff.
我恨倒立零钱会从我的兜里掉出来
I just hate itwhen the change falls out of my pocket.
嘿 那个人想跟你说话
Hey, man,I think these guys want to talk to you.
拦住他!
Hold it!
我会告诉哈里斯上尉的!
Capt. Harris will hear about this!
进来
Come.
- 长官 - 科普兰 出什么事了?
- Sir. - Copeland, what the hell happened to you?
一些玩滑板的小阿飞在商业街制造混乱
Some skateboard punksstarted a riot at the mall.
把他们带来
Bring them in here.
- 他们跑了 - 跑了?
- They got away. - They got away?
- 我尽全力了 长官 - 这不够 知道吗 科普兰!
- I did the best I could, sir. - It wasn't enough, was it, Copeland?
- 知道 长官 - 我来亲手解决一下这些小流氓
- No, sir. - I'll handle these punks personally.
- 是 长官 - 我要三辆警车…
- Yes, sir. - I want three patrol cars...
把这片儿管住科普兰 我的帽子!
dissecting the neighborhood.Copeland, my hat!
- 是 长官 - 你 呼叫所有的摩托骑警
- Yes, sir. - You, radio - alert all motorcycle units.
我要你们撒开大网把那些小兔崽子们当场抓住!
I want a chopper in the air.Spot these boys on the ground.
学监 跟着我
Proctor, ride with me.
- 动起来 快! - 来了 长官
- Now, Proctor, move it! - Coming, sir.
马上来!
Be right there!
他们往那边走了!
There they go!
倒车 小声点!
Back it up. Quiet!
我说了 小声点 白痴!
I said quiet, dickhead.
我们就要把他们抓住了
We've got them now.
我知道他们来过这
I know they came in here.
6号车呼叫哈里斯上尉我们在小巷一端发现他们
Unit 6 to Capt. Harris.We've got them at the end of the alley.
抓住你们了!
I got you now!
控制住他们 我们马上到
You hold them right there. We're coming.
科普兰 抓住他们了吗?
Copeland, have you got them?
女士们先生们 晚上好!我是警察学校的凯瑞·马霍尼
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.I'm Carey Mahoney of the Police Academy.
谢谢 非常感谢 真是太感谢了 你们真热情
Thank you. Thank you very much.Please. Thank you. You're too kind.
是哈里斯 还有他的笨帮手 快!
It's Harris. Haul ass. Go.
我要抓住你们 你们这些小阿飞
I got you, you little punks.
不许动 你们两个小流氓!把你的手从我的屁股上拿开!
Freeze, you little hoodlums.Get your hands off my ass, Proctor.
滚开 学监!
Get away, Proctor.
不! 别摇栅栏!
No. Don't shake the fence.
噢 混蛋! 不!
Oh, shit. No!
这项计划的目的…
The purpose of this program...
是为了形成更好的工作关系 在我们警方与…
is to develop a better working relationshipbetween us, the police...
当他说到"好了 姑娘们、小伙们"的时候我们就…
When he says, "Okay, boys and girls,"we're all gonna....
…与你们 社会公民之间
...and you, the community.
停下! 停下! 给我停下!
Stop! Stop right there!
而且最重要的是 这是前所未有的
You see, the great thing is, this is a first.
警察学校负责对你们的培训使得你们能更好地保护自己
The Police Academy has offered to trainyou citizens to better protect yourselves.
- 你们会成为领导新潮的人 - 我们会有枪吗?
- You'll be trendsetters. - Do we get to pack heat?
枪——
Heat - -
抓住那些小流氓! 抓住他们!
Stop those little punks! Stop them!
你们被捕了
You're under arrest!
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
谁笑呢? 你们两个傻瓜!
Who's laughing now, you little twits?
你们的衣服让我恶心!我会马上让你们明白明白
And your clothes make me want to puke.I'll tell you that right now.
- 哈里斯上尉! - 噢 噢 是马霍尼
- Capt. Harris! - Well, well, Mahoney.
- 好久不见 长官 - 可不是
- It's been a long time, sir. - So it has.
还有快嘴琼斯
Well, Motormouth Jones.
有人向您说过您的裁缝很棒吗 长官?
Anyone ever tell youyou've got a great tailor, sir?
我上周就说过
I mentioned that just last week.
马霍尼 有人对你说过你还是个尿裤子的小屁孩儿吗?
Has anyone told you, Mahoney,that you're still a little pissant?
- 别人的看法无关紧要 长官 - 阿尼和凯尔做了什么?
- No one whose opinion matters, sir. - What did Arnie and Kyle do?
你认识这两个小丑? 我早该猜到
You know those clowns?I should have figured.
你的两个小朋友毁了一辆警车还有购物中心…
Your little pals wrecked a police car,destroyed a shopping mall...
骚扰公众 还使劲反抗
harassed citizens, resisted arrest.
放松点 上尉 他们只是些疯疯颠颠的小孩儿
Go easy, Captain. They're just wacky kids.
哼 我们倒要看看他们在监狱里还怎么疯疯颠颠
We'll see how those wacky kidslike it in jail.
我在这个位置上这么多年见过各式各样的扰乱公共罪
In all my years on the bench,I have seen all sorts of public disorder.
年轻人应该学会如何去遵守…
Young people must learn to conform...
文明社会的规范与法律
to the standards and lawsof civilized society.
根据证词 再考虑到…
In reviewing the testimonyand taking into account...
你们对于公共与私人财产的漠视…
your disregardfor public and private property...
我只能出一个结论：
I can reach only one decision:
罪恶滔天!
Guilty as hell.
你! 你想把我毁掉!
You flushed me down the toilet!
在你们被宣判之前…
Before you pass sentence - -
他们想把我送进监狱!然后那些肥胖的、浑身是毛的家伙就要…
They're gonna send me to jail,and some fat, hairy guy is gonna - -
- 我能到台前跟您说几句话吗 法官大人? - 可以 中士
- May I approach the bench, Your Honor? - Yes, Sergeant.
法官大人 我们真的要把这些孩子送到监狱里吗?
Sir, do we want to expose these boys,these children to a prison environment?
- 是的 - 上尉 能不能让我管理自己的法庭?
- Yes. - May I run my own court, Captain?
- 你有更好的主意吗? - 是的 法官大人
- You've got a better idea? - Yes, I do, sir.
拉萨指挥官发起了一项新的公共关系计划
Comdt. Lassard has initiateda new community relations program.
为什么不让这些孩子…
Why not assign these kids...
通过参加这项计划而替代受刑呢?
to that programas a form of alternate sentencing?
- 这太荒唐了! - 我会判定的
- That's ridiculous! - I'll be the judge of that.
我…打扰一下
I.... Excuse me.
我对这项计划很有兴趣
I like the sound of thiscommunity relations gig.
我是米尔特·巴特尔沃斯 普通人的辩护律师
Milt Butterworth,defender of the common man.
法官大人 看看控诉清单吧!
Your Honor, look at this list of complaints.
让我直接来引用您的话说就是…
And I quote you directly, sir, when I say - -
嘿 长官 我觉得你一张嘴就是在蔑视法庭
Gee, sir, I thought you only gotcontempt of court for opening your mouth.
马霍尼 我警告你
Mahoney, I'm warning you.
在我的地盘上别想实行拉萨的计划
You keep Lassard's C.O.Psout of my precinct.
长官 您不明白我所要做的
You don't understandwhat I'm trying to do.
我清楚得很
I understandexactly what you're trying to do.
把他们赶出去 尤其是这两个小混蛋
Just keep them out,especially these two little buttwads.
对不起 先生 您不是要…
Excuse me, sir,but you're not planning to attack us...
打我们吧 啊?
with any more of your bodily functions,are you?
你只要明白 我们永远不会再见面了 永远
You just make surethat we never meet again. Ever.
知道吗 有了这两个家伙拉萨的计划永远也不会成功的
You know, with those two idiotsin Lassard's program, it'll never work.
对不起 先生
Excuse me, sir.
我们想找一位叫费尔德曼的女士
We're looking for a Mrs. Feldman.
- 您知道这个人吗? - 知道
- Do you know her? - Yes.
对不起 女士您认识罗依斯女士吗?
Excuse me, ma'am.Do you know a Mrs. Lois - -
- 请问我们在哪可以找到罗依斯·费尔德曼? - 那儿
- Where can we find Lois Feldman, please? - There.
谢谢
Thank you.
费尔德曼女士?
Mrs. Feldman?
- 是谁? - 警察
- Who's asking? - Police.
是关于那些该死的图书馆的书吗?
Is it about those damn library books?
我们是来跟您谈关于"全民警察"计划的
We're following up on your allegedinterest in the Citizens On Patrol program.
那我就是费尔德曼女士了 请进
Then I'm Mrs. Feldman. Come on in.
卡拉汉 小心你的屁股
Callahan, cover your rear.
您的品味真让人钦佩!
I admire your taste.
噢 这都是我自己布置的
Yes, well, I do all my own decorating.
您在这方面很有天赋 女士
You have a talent for it, ma'am.
我一会儿就来 警官
I'll be with you in a moment, Sarge.
也许您愿意先谈一下这项计划 女士
Perhaps you'd like to discussthe program first, ma'am.
还有什么可谈的?
What's to discuss?
你觉得我会呆在这任凭动脉硬化吗?
Think I want to hang out hereand listen to arteries hardening?
我把防弹背心放哪儿了?
Where did I put that bulletproof vest?
好 集合! 快点! 整队!
All right, fall in! Come on, please, line up.
快! 赶紧排好队!
Come on, I need a lineup here.
你好 女士 女士们先生们…
Hello, ma'am. Ladies and gentlemen - -
- 谢谢您… - 费尔德曼女士
- Thank you, Miss.... - Mrs. Feldman.
欢迎你们到学校来
I want to welcome all of youto the Academy.
你们将参加这项新的、令人振奋的计划我叫它 叫它…
You are part of a newand exciting program that I call...
- "全民警察"计划 - "全民警察"计划
- C.O.P. - C.O.P.
- 全市公民作为警察巡逻计划 - 全市公民作为警察巡逻计划
- Citizens On Patrol. - Citizens On Patrol.
- 全市公民作为警察巡逻计划! - 全市公民作为警察巡逻计划!
- Citizens On Patrol! - Citizens On Patrol!
你们将会和警察们一起工作、训练
You will work and train with the police.
警察将会和你们一起工作、训练
The police will work and train with you.
工作、训练；训练、工作
Working and training,training and working.
对不起 指挥官
Excuse me, Commandant.
但你们期望公众来做警察的工作吗?
But do you expect the communityto do the job of the police force?
工作多得很 适合的人也多得是
There are many, many jobsfor many, many people.
长官 这事交给我吧
Sir, I'll take care of this.
对不起 年轻的女士 指挥官的意思是…
Excuse me, young lady,what the Commandant means...
这项计划会促进…
is that this programwill promote understanding...
公众与警方之间的理解…
between the community and the police...
并使得公众在预防犯罪时更为主动
and make the communitymore active in crime prevention.
主动? 哪道这样不危险吗?
Active in crime prevention?Won't that be dangerous?
不 我们只是教他们…
No. We just want to teach citizens...
制止犯罪的发生
to prevent crimes from taking place.
从理论上听起来不错 希望实际中也能如此
It sounds fine in theory.Let's hope it works in practice.
我喜欢他 他真的是一条很棒的鱼
I like him. He's a really nice fish.
他看上去有点像您
He looks a little like you.
我将要参加在伦敦举行的一场国际会议
I will attendan international police seminar in London.
如果我可以把…
It would bethe crowning achievement of my career...
全世界的警察教师集中到这里向他们展示我的…
if I could close this seminar...
已经顺利实施了的"全民警察"计划并以此来结束这次会议…
by bringing instructorsfrom all around the world...
这将成为我职业生涯中的最高成就
here to watchthe C.O.P. program in action.
我将寄希望于你们 来成就我的这一梦想
I'm counting on all of youto make that possible.
在拉萨校长不在的期间…
In Comdt. Lassard's absence...
我将指定一个强壮且富有经验的警官…
I've appointed a very able - bodiedand experienced officer...
来管理学校
to run the Academy.
啊 时间正好 他来了
Perfect timing. Here he is now.
立正!
Attention!
哈里斯掌权两周? 可恶!
Two weeks of Harris? Damn!
噢!
Damn.
除臭剂? 谢谢
Deodorant? Thanks.
这里乱七八糟的 赶紧给我收拾干净!
Straighten this mess up.
- 哪乱? - 赶快!
- What mess? - Now!
我要你们这群臭东西还有参加那个"全民警察"计划的人…
I want all of you dirtbagsand that group of C.O.P. people...
下午两点在宿舍外集合!
out in front of this dormitoryat 1400 hours.
快快快 动起来!
Move it!
长官 我们正在谈论您的声音是如何的圆润
Sir, we were just commentingon how you'd mellowed.
- 上尉? - 什么事 马霍尼?
- Captain? - What is it, Mahoney?
我希望您能给这项计划一个公平的机会
I hope you're gonnagive this program a fair chance.
这个计划跟你一样 马霍尼 糟糕透顶
This program, Mahoney,is just like you: a bad idea.
那是您的意见 长官
That's your opinion, sir.
这是拉萨校长的计划 而且这是他的学校
But this is Comdt. Lassard's idea,and his Academy.
事情是可以改变的 马霍尼
Things can change, Mahoney.
是的 事情是可以改变的
Yes, things can change.
我们外面见
I'll see you out front.
我打赌您感觉神清气爽 长官
I bet that was refreshing, sir.
在这两周里…
Over the next two weeks...
你们会经历一个改良的计划
you'll go througha modified training program.
你们会学到很多很多重要的用以防止犯罪的知识
You'll learn many, many keysto crime prevention.
你们也可以教会你们周围很多很多的朋友
Keys you can teach many, many othersin your community.
改良? 改什么? 我要工作
Modified? Modified nothing.I want the works.
- 没错! - 女士…
- Yeah. - Madam...
是摆事实讲道理的时候了
I think it's time for a dose of reality.
你们会忘记拉萨的大肆宣传
You can forget Lassard's hype.
你们不属于这里
You people do not belong here.
尤其是你 还有你
Especially you and you.
社会行动团体只意味着一件事情 仅仅一件
Community action groups mean one thing,and one thing only.
我希望那不是口香糖
I hope that wasn't gum.
听见上尉说什么了吗? 那是什么?
You heard the Captain. Is it?
真的是口香糖 长官! 还是泡泡糖樱桃味的 我想
It's definitely gum, sir. Bubble gum.Cherry, I think.
- 非常感谢 学监! - 别客气 长官
- Thank you, Proctor. - You're welcome, sir.
这些团体只意味着公民妨碍警察公务
These groups only meancitizens getting in the way of the police.
现在 我不想跟你们扯上关系
Now, I don't get involvedin your business...
你们也别干扰我的——
and I don't want you involved in my - -
嗯 如果你们聪明的话…
Now, if you were smart...
就该乖乖回家 把这个馊点子彻底忘掉…
you would go homeand forget this stupid idea....
嘿 我是听到婚礼上的钟声了吗?
Are those wedding bells I hear, sir?
- 这该死的杂种狗是谁的? - 这该死的杂种狗是我的
- Whose damn mutt is this? - It's my damn mutt.
我要它从这消失!
I want him out of here!
- 但是 长官… - 快消失!
- But, sir - - - Out!
我才不会把克拉伦斯赶走 它是我的宠物
I am not getting rid of Clarence.He's my pet.
为什么要? 再说了 哈里斯还有学监
Why should you?After all, Harris has Proctor.
让我来照顾他
I'll take him.
我有一所大房子 漂亮的后院
I have a big house, nice yard.
看 他喜欢我 我们会相处很好的
See, he likes me. We'll get along fine.
我怎么样? 我经过训练的
Me, too? I'm housebroken.
好了伙计们 站到白线前来!
Come on, C.O.Ps,let's step up to the white line!
排成一队 然后听琼斯长官训话
Let's line ourselves up with a slot,then let's listen to Mr. Jones.
谢谢 塔克贝利中士
Thank you, Sgt. Tackleberry.
这是点38口径标准警务用枪
This is a standard police issue.38.
仔细检查你就会发现…
Examine this weapon carefully.
里面并没有装上子弹
You must be surethis weapon is not loaded.
无论是否装填子弹 你们都要开始对它负责
You will be responsible for the loadingand unloading of this weapon yourself.
现在 塔克贝利中士
Now, Sgt. Tackleberry.
你们要成为持枪一族
You want to become one with the gun.
感受它…爱抚它…
Feel the gun, caress the gun...
直到使它成为你生命、呼吸、活动…
until it's a living, breathing, vibrating...
的延伸
extension of yourself.
我找女人也是这样
I look for the same in a woman.
嘿 这玩意儿没装子弹
This sucker's not loaded.
你用不着玩真的
You won't be using live ammo.
塔克 让我用你的宝贝玩意儿耍几下 怎么样?
Tack, how about letting me squeeze offa few rounds of that baby?
塔克?
Tack?
当然可以 女士
Affirmative, Mrs. F.
现在当心 因为点44的大酒瓶有很大的…
Now, be carefulbecause a.44 magnum has quite a...
后坐力
kick.
嘿 真他妈的有趣!
Damn, that was fun!
解救溺水者
Rescuing the drowning victim.
当接近潜在的危险的和…
Now, when approachinga potentially dangerous...
不受控制的受害者时 只能这样划水
and out - of - control victim,use this stroke only.
胳膊展开用于保护
Arms out of the way for protection.
现在 当你抓住溺水者的时候胳膊划过他的胸部…
Now, when you get the victim in control,you slip your arm across his chest...
伸到他另一侧胳膊下
under his opposite arm.
让他的头和颈靠在你的肩上
Rest his head and his neckagainst your shoulder.
用脚蹬水这时 溺水者可能会挣扎
Kick with your feet.Now, your victim could be struggling.
挣扎一下 大房子 很好 大房子…
Struggle, House. Good, House....
大房子!
House!
真敏捷! 我去救他!
Really swift! I'll get him!
阿尼! 给我上来! 你就是犯罪女神!
Arnie, get out of the pool! You just ate!
把他弄上来!
Get him out of here!
谢谢 朋友
Thanks, pal.
现在我们来进行游水安全课
Now we have an opportunityto start our water safety lesson.
我将扮演溺水者
I will play the drowning victim.
现在 谁来救我?
Now, who's going to save me?
- 噢! 我来! - 我来!
- Yeah! - Yeah!
您真是很勇敢 我、我很佩服
That was mighty brave. I admire that.
那没什么
That was nothing.
你有吹风机或、或、或是摩丝吗?
You don't have a hair dryer,or perhaps some mousse?
没有 你的头发看上去很棒 很、很、很时髦
No. Your hair looks nice. It's very stylish.
（法语）我? 时髦吗?
Moi?Stylish?
我想我该走了
I think I'd better be going.
米奇!
Mickey!
他死了! 是他杀了他!
He's dead! He killed him!
- 我想学校会赔偿的 - 那我的感情怎么赔偿?
- I'm sure the Academy will pay for it. - What about the sentimental value?
这是我的传家宝
This is a family heirloom here.
这是我当警察前偷的最后一样东西
This is the last thing I ever stolebefore joining the Academy.
这到底是怎么回事? 坠入爱河的学员?
What the hell is this? Cadets in heat?
不 我们只是喜欢谈天
No. We were just, like, talking.
嗯 "只是"、"喜欢" 换个地方谈去!
Just, like, talk somewhere else.
这不是产卵池! 我要的是纪律!
This is not a spawning pool.I want discipline.
明白了吗 泽得?
Do I make myself clear, Zed?
纪律!
Discipline!
- 怪物 - 什么?
- Jerk. - What?
他说再见
He said bye.
不 不 我说、说的是"怪物"我想我的意思很明白
No. I said jerk. I think it was pretty clear.
- 我说："怪物" - 怪物
- I said, "Jerk." - Jerk.
学员们 我想跟你们讨论一下…
Cadets, I'd now like to discuss with you...
一些至关重要的事情…
something that will bevital for you to know...
当你们作为警察并外出巡逻时
when you're, like, out there on the jobas a police officer.
这才是正确的吃油炸圈饼的方法
And that's the correct wayto eat a doughnut.
- 一个油炸圈饼—— - 立正!
- A doughnut - - - Attention!
哈里斯上尉
Capt. Harris.
从现在起 任何人再把梅斯气放错地方的话…
From this moment on, anyonewho misplaces their canister of Mace...
都会遭到惩罚!
will be reprimanded and fined.
- 明白了吗? - 是 长官!
- Is that clear? - Yes, sir!
再见
Bye.
作为市民警察…
As Citizens On Patrol...
耐心和长命对你们来说很重要
endurance and longevityshould be very important to you.
有氧运动会让你们保持身材…
Aerobic activity will keep you in shape...
心脏更加有力
and keep that heart rate up.
音乐会使痛苦减轻
Music, however,makes it a little less painful.
胡克丝 磁带
Hooks, cassette.
我相信胡克丝中士给大家选择了合适的音乐
I have confidence that Sgt. Hookshas chosen the appropriate music.
噢噢 没有磁带
No cassette.
好 开始
Let's go.
挑得不错 胡克丝 好吧
Nice selection, Hooks. All right.
慢慢走 慢慢开始
Slow walk. Slow start.
动动胳膊 嗯 很好
Keep your arms moving. That's good.
逐渐慢跑 很好!
Into a nice slow jog. Okay!
胳膊动起来! 保持呼吸! 别忘了呼吸!
Arms moving. Keep breathing.Don't forget to breathe.
收腹 胡克丝 好啊! 一起来!
Tuck his tummy, Hooks. Attagirl. Let's go.
现在 这只哨子会相当重要…
Now, this whistle can be very valuable...
在你身处困境时
when walking througha bad neighborhood.
如果你的钱包被抢 吹哨子…
If your purse gets snatched,blow this whistle...
来提醒你的邻居或是警察 他们就能赶来帮你
to alert your neighbors and the policeso they can help.
费尔德曼女士 你能来表演受害者吗?
Now, Mrs. Feldman,would you play the victim?
- 当然 - 很好 我呢 扮成抢包的
- Yes. - Okay, and I'll be Mr. Purse Snatcher.
- 好的 - 开始
- Okay. - Go.
还有问题吗?
Any questions?
现在 练习
Now, practice.
你把他打倒了 差不多 一分钟他害怕了 他 差不多 退缩了
You had him for, like, a minute.He was scared. He was, like, flinching.
他的脸变…
His face went....
抱歉
Sorry.
"全民警察" 真是个笑话
Citizens On Patrol. What a joke.
- 你知道"全民警察"到底什么意思吗? - 不 长官 什么意思?
- You know what C.O.P. really stands for? - No, sir. What?
- 全市爱尿裤子的民众当警察计划 这不可笑! - 是 长官!
- Collection Of Pissants. That's not funny. - No, sir.
这种市民运动就是灾难! 是个馊点子!我会证明的
This citizen - action crap is a disaster,a bad idea, and I'm going to prove it.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
对不起 所有人 注意一下
Excuse me, everyone.
我是说 不是所有人
I mean, not everyone.
立正! 对不起 让开!
Attention! Excuse me. Move it!
- 所有人 过来! - 胡克丝
- Everybody, come over here! - Hooks.
别再让警部难堪 回到你的文员队伍里去!
Stop embarrassing the Police Departmentand join your civilian buddies.
听好了 请注意一下!胡克丝 罐子!
May I have your attention, please?Hooks, the tank!
- 对不起 - 你个傻瓜!
- I'm so sorry. - You dimwit!
（氦气）
今天 胡克丝 今天
Today, Hooks, today.
现在 带着你的小细嗓从这滚开!
Now, take your little munchkin voiceand go away.
听着!
Listen up!
这是使用氧气的正确程序
This is the proper procedurefor administering oxygen.
先把面罩仔细地戴在病人脸上…
You place the mask securelyabout the face of the patient...
然后让他们深呼吸
and then have them breathe deeply.
这才是在哈里斯上尉地盘上的正确做法
Now, that is the way it's donein Capt. Harris' precinct.
怎么搞的? 胡克丝!
What the hell? Hooks!
嘿 绅士们 你们觉得你们是在度假吗?
So you gentlemen thinkyou're on a vacation?
你们不比别人强 快 动起来 该干活了!
You're no better than anyone else,so let's go, let's get to work.
嘿 花花公子 快起来!
Come on, dudes, chill out.
你们这些小哥在做坏榜样!
You dudes are setting a bad example.
听不见你说什么 哥们!没瞧见 睡美人正在睡觉吗?
Can't hear you, bro. Can't you seeI'm getting my beauty sleep?
对不起
I'm sorry.
起来!
Move it!
你绝对让他们长了见识
You sure told them.
你就没想过…或许该试试隐形眼镜…
Did you ever think aboutmaybe getting some contact lenses...
或是其它的什么…嗯…差不多的东西吗?
or something, like, you know?
那样你会看上去更俊些
You'd look good in them.
学监 这是条小巷
Proctor, this is an alley.
我知道 长官 但这是马霍尼给我的指南
I know, sir, but these are the directionsMahoney gave me.
- 马霍尼? - 是的 长官
- Mahoney? - Yes, sir.
他说这家餐馆的色拉全城第一
He says this restauranthas the best salad bar in town.
嗯 这他妈最好是真的
It damn sure better have.
- 学监? - 什么事 长官?
- Proctor. - Yes, sir?
我没看到有色拉吧台
I don't see a salad bar.
看 也许他们卖海味
Look, maybe they serve seafood.
这并不可笑 你个白痴
That's not funny, you idiot.
你在看什么? 你个混蛋!
What are you looking at, you peckerhead?
制服不错!
Nice uniform.
弄得我也想穿上我的海军服了
Makes me wish I'd worn my sailor outfit.
我要离开这 让开 让开!
I'm getting out of here. Move it!
我想半途走开是不允许的 长官
I don't think cutting in is allowed, sir.
项圈不错!
Nice collar.
又来了 新一局马霍尼带球迂回前进…
Here we go again. Next round.Mahoney weaving his way through...
看上去真棒! 绕过后卫
looking pretty good.Gets past the main defense.
然后…经胯下投篮!
And, under the leg!
噢 好球!
Nice shot!
这家伙是个运动高手 人群都为之疯狂了!
That man is a hot dog.The crowd's gone wild!
球又进了又来了 我们又拿到了球
The ball's brought in.Here we go. We have the play going.
投给泽得
Throws to Zed.
有些争抢
A little bit of a steal there.
马霍尼又传球给高塔
Mahoney throws a pass to Hightower.
然后高塔他…用力的一记扣篮!
And then Hightower he....The Doctor of Dunk scores!
你杀了它! 太恨了!
You killed it. Really swift!
噢 公众运动
Some community action.
女士们先生们 这位是学监 一位犹太支持者!
Ladies and gentlemen,it's Lt. Proctor, a ghetto favorite!
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you very much.
我很荣幸成为…
I'm honored to be - -
你知道 哈里斯上尉是不会喜欢这种…
You know,Capt. Harris isn't gonna like this...
吊儿郎当的事情的
goofing off.
- 噢 行啦 这是增进群众关系 - 不不不 马霍尼
- Come on. This is community relations. - No, Mahoney.
我是这方面的专家 这就是吊儿郎当
I'm an expert in goofing off,and this is goofing off.
我会报告哈里斯上尉的
And I'm gonna have to tell him.
- 我有一种把他掰成两半的冲动 - 为什么呢?
- I have an urge to break him in half. - Why fight it?
不 高塔 别激动 大个儿他不值得你这么做
No, Hightower. Take it easy, big guy.The creep's not worth it.
- 你用完了? - 是的 请吧
- You through in there? - Sure, go ahead.
谢谢
Thanks.
喂 西尔韦奥?
Excuse me, Silvio?
我想能否请你帮个忙我这需要帮忙
I wonder if you can help me.I need some help over here.
- 就那 - 没问题
- Right there. - No problem.
嘿 别着急 我一会儿就完!
Hold your horses, I'll be out in a minute!
好 我喜欢 这边点儿
Okay, like, bring it in.
一点 好 再过来一丁点!
Just, like, bring it in a hair.
小心飞机!
Watch out for the plane!
噢 真有同情心!
Oh, the humanity!
嗯 完美 不 太精细了
Okay, that's perfect. No, that's fine.
- 地铁警察 - 特殊任务
- Metro police. - Special assignment.
女士们先生们…
Ladies and gentlemen...
奏国歌 请起立!
please rise for our national anthem.
- 念关于我的那段 阿尼 - 哪段?
- Read that part about me again, Arnie. - What part?
你知道 就是关于"全民警察"计划活力四射的领军人物的那段
You know, the part aboutthe dynamic leader of the C.O.P.
说对了! 那指的就是我!
Get real! That's me they're talking about.
晚上好 先生们我祝贺你们又度过了美好的一天
Good evening, gentlemen.I congratulate you on another good day.
睡个好觉
Sleep well.
嘿 伯爵 担心我们马上就要聊完了是吗?
Count, getting worriedwe're gonna be taking over soon?
我们准备好了
We're ready.
你们正在进步 但你们仍然在食物链的底端
You're improving, guys. But you're stillway down in the food chain.
现在吸血鬼说："熄灯了 小鬼们"
As we vampires say, "Lights out, suckers."
这项计划简单得很
This C.O.P. bit is a breeze.
- 我们准备好了 - 我同意
- We are ready. - I concur.
我觉得我们已经能够粉碎任何现实中的犯罪
I think we're ready to bustsome truly major criminals.
也许我们该出去找一些…
Maybe we should go out and find some....
- 也许我们该成为义务警员 - 对 就是它 义务警员!
- Maybe we should become vigilantes. - Yeah, that's it. Vigilantes.
快起床! 我们现在需要你们!
Wake up, men! We need you. Now!
快点!
Come on.
- 出什么事了? 我们要去哪? - 为什么我们要来这? 出什么事了?
- What's going on? Where are we going? - Why are we here? What's happening?
你们来这是因为你们已经准备好了你们自己这么说的
You're here because you're ready.You said you were ready.
- 有件事 我—— - 你已经准备好了
- One thing l - - - You're ready, now.
你能把我们现在的任务解释地详细一点儿吗?
Could you be a little more specificconcerning our current mission?
- 我们已经掌握了两个重要罪犯 - 嗯 我现在想回家
- We're apprehending two known felons. - I'll be going home now.
- 其他人呢? - 什么其他人? 就我们
- Where are the rest? - What rest? We're it.
- 我们将把他们从楼里赶出来 - 你们在小巷里呆着 断绝他们的退路
- We'll flush them out of the building. - You stay behind, cut them off in the alley.
呆着
Stay.
嘿 那枪呢?
What about guns and shit, man?
枪? 不 你们不需要枪
Guns? No, you won't be needing them.
我们很肯定他们没有武器
We're pretty sure they're not armed.
你知道 他们没有我们也会处理好的我们只会妨碍他们
They can handle this without us.We'll just get in the way, you know.
说的好
Good thinking.
我们抓到他们了!
We got them, men!
没事了 伙计们 过来吧!
It's all right, men. Come on over.
好了 你们三个将跟巴杜拉一起坐在车后…
All right, you threewill be riding in the back with Badula...
还有他死去的兄弟
and his late brother.
你们几个看住他
You guys keep him subdued.
走
Let's go.
别让他的巫术吓着你
Don't let his voodoomumbo jumbo scare you.
笨蛋! 以为他们能杀死巴杜拉的兄弟
Fools. To thinkthey can kill the brother of Badula.
我从没这么想
I never thought that.
我能将手伸进牦牛的体内然后撕裂它的心!
That I could reach into the belly of a yakand rip out his heart.
这能让他复生吗?
That would bring him back to life?
不 我只是饿了
No, man. I'm hungry.
听着 我们去买些汉堡和著条 一会儿就回来
Listen, we're going for some burgersand fries. We'll be right back.
不管我的事!
Out of my way!
我猜他们根本不像他们自己想的那样已经准备好了
I guess they weren't as readyas they thought they were.
行了 塔克 可以摘掉面具了
You can take the mask off now, Tack.
- 学监? - 什么事 长官?
- Proctor. - Yes, sir?
- 这些人是干什么来的? - 来参加聚会 长官
- Who are all these people? - They're here for the party, sir.
什么聚会?
What party?
噢 一些计划的学员邀请了他们的一些朋友…
A few of the Citizens On Patrol membersinvited a few of their friends...
然后他们又请了他们的一些朋友您看见了 就是这样 长官
and they invited a few of their friends.You know how it goes, sir.
- 聚会? - 是的 长官
- A party? - Yes, sir.
聚会? 为什么没人告诉我?
A party? Why wasn't I told?
马霍尼!
嘿 卡拉汉! 嘿 胡克丝!
Hey, Callahan. Hey, Hooks.
注意了 女士们先生们!
Attention, ladies and gentlemen!
女士们先生们 请注意一下!
Ladies and gentlemen,can I please have your attention?
感谢你们的到来!
I'd like to thank you all for coming!
让我们一起狂欢吧!
Let's party!
- 让开 你们这些同性恋! - 对不起
- Move those patooties. - Excuse me.
所有警员都给我从池子里上来!
All police officers out of the pool!
快 上来 所有人都上来!
Let's go! Out, everybody out!
长官 为什么您就不能让大家快活一些呢?
Sir, why don't you justlet everyone enjoy themselves?
你为什么就不能亲亲我粉嫩嫩的屁股呢 马霍尼?
Why don't you justkiss my rosy red ass, Mahoney?
粉嫩嫩的?
Rosy?
从池子里给我出来!
Get out of that pool now!
瞧瞧你的样子!
Just look at yourself.
你玷污了这身警服! 去换了它 快!
You are a disgrace to the uniform!Go get changed. Move it.
- 我们在找什么? - 这个
- What are we looking for? - This.
- 噢 哈里斯上尉 - 马特森小姐
- Why, Capt. Harris. - Miss Mattson.
- 您好 - 您好吗?
- Hello. - How are you?
您看见克拉伦斯了吗?
Have you seen Clarence?
您别想让那个虱子窝靠近我
Don't you let that fleabag near me.
克拉伦斯为你疯狂 上尉让我把他叫过来
Clarence is crazy about you, Captain.Let me just call him over.
- 不! - 就一小会儿?
- No. - For a second?
- 不! - 那好吧 再见
- No. - Okay. Bye.
别再裂着嘴坏笑! 臭屁篓子! 解散!
Wipe those grins off your faces,buttbreaths! Dismissed!
伯曼医生 请接二号分机伯曼医生 请接二号分机
Dr. Berman, please pick up line two.Dr. Berman, line two, please.
- 你不该来这 - 哈里斯上尉怎么样了?
- You shouldn't be in here. - How is Capt. Harris?
- 我们做了我们所能做的 - 求您了 轻一点
- We'll do all we can. - Please, be gentle.
我听见哈里斯说的了 他说的都是错的
I heard what Harris said, and he's wrong.
这种事总是发生在我身上人们根本不理解我
It happens to me all the time.People just don't understand me.
也许你说话的时候慢一点、轻一点…
Maybe if you talked a little slower,a little softer....
我不是这个意思 我是说人们并不了解我的为人
That's not what I meant. I meantpeople don't know who I really am.
我想我现在也得注意一下我的措辞 是吗?
Now I got to worry about my diction, too?
- 我的句子结构怎么样? - 完美极了
- How's my sentence structure? - Perfect.
事实上 我觉得你才是完美的
In fact, I think you're just about perfect.
我觉得我要吐了
I think I'm going to puke.
嗨 长官 感觉怎么样?
Hi, sir. How are you feeling?
我要等着这倒霉的胶水慢慢剥落
I have to waitfor the damn glue to wear off.
我没听清
I didn't catch that.
您是说："把这倒霉的手套脱掉"吗?
Was that, "the dim shoot to snare off"?
我说我要等着这倒霉的胶水慢慢剥落
I said I have to waitfor the damn glue to wear off.
于是我问她："你一直在指挥台底下工作吗? "
So I asked her,"Do you always work under podiums?"
指挥官?
Commandant?
噢 赫斯特长官! 真是惊喜啊!
Why, Chief Hurst,this is a splendid, splendid surprise!
还记得从日本来的Nogata吗?他是我们代表团的成员
You remember Nogata?He's part of our Japanese contingent.
这是赫斯特长官
This is Chief Hurst.
我们听说过很多很多关于您和您的城市的美好的事情
We have heard many, manywonderful things about you and your city.
我在帮他们提高英语水平
I've been helping them with their English.
- 请坐 请 - 谢谢
- Please, sit. Please. - Thank you.
我希望有机会您们能直接来参观我们美丽的城市
I hope you'll find the timeto see our beautiful city firsthand.
事实上 我亲自到这里来…
In fact, I've just flown here personally...
传达市长的邀请…
to extend the Mayor's invitation...
想看一看我的…
to see my....
看一看拉萨指挥官的社团计划的开展情况
To see Comdt. Lassard'scommunity program in action.
我们深信这项计划将成为…
We are convincedthat this program will serve...
全世界各个城市为之学习的榜样
as a model for cities around the world.
我们非常荣幸接受市长的邀请
We would be honoredto accept your invitation.
- 太好了 - 请跟我来
- Wonderful. - Please, come.
- （德）再见 - （意）再会
- Auf Wiedersehen. - Arrivederci.
（法）再见
Bonsoir.
我看你不仅仅只教了他们英语
I see you've been teaching themsomething other than English.
我只是尽我所能
I do what I can.
- 嗯 我的计划真得运行了吗? - 该死 是的
- So my program is really, really working? - Hell, yes.
从明天起 "全民警察"计划全面实施!
Starting tomorrow,C.O.Ps will be working the streets.
紧急情况 费尔德曼请求帮助
C.O.P. emergency. Feldman here.
请到克拉克大街和麦因大街交汇处的仓库来!
Meet me at the corner ofClark and Main Street at the warehouse.
小心 费女士
10 - 4, Mrs. F.
- 40美元 成交吗? - 好的 40
- $40, we're agreed? - Okay, $40.
照几张像做证据
Snap off a few shots for evidence.
离近点儿
Get closer.
我在希尔大街的布鲁斯商店见过这是买卖脏物
I saw this on Hill Street Blues.It's a fencing operation.
你会喜欢这些的 我们刚刚卸了一卡车的货
You're gonna love these.We just unloaded a van full of them.
好的 把其余的也拿来吧
Okay, bring in the rest of it.
下个箱子
Next case.
相机挺棒 少于80别卖给那帮骗子
Nice camera.Don't let that crook give you less than $80.
不许动 你们这些邋遢鬼!
Freeze, you scuzzbuckets!
公民警察! 伙计们 上 抓住他们!
This is a citizen's arrest. Get them, boys!
呆在这不许动 等警察来
You're not moving till the cops get here.
我就是警察 女士
I am the cops, lady.
三个月的训练 肉体与精神上的考验
Three months' workout the window, down the drain.
你们这些参加计划的学员正等待着…
Your Citizens On Patrol just screwed up...
在这座城市历史中 唯一的、规模最大的、秘密的…
the single biggestundercover police sting operation...
让人头疼的警界行动…!
in the history of this city!
告诉他们这个好消息 长官
Tell them the good news, sir.
- 谢谢 学监 - 别客气 长官
- Thank you, Proctor. - You're welcome, sir.
从现在起"全民警察"计划被暂缓执行…
As of now,the C.O.P. program is suspended...
等待再做决定!
pending a full investigation.
立正!
Attention!
马霍尼 我真的、真的太为你所做的一切骄傲了!
Mahoney, I'm so, so proudof the job you've done.
干得好!
Nice work, men.
全世界的目光都集中在这项计划上
The eyes of the world are on this program.
对不起 长官 我想我们得谈谈
Excuse me, sir. I think we should talk.
这一地区必须和各式的犯罪打交道…
This precinct must deal withevery type of criminal...
从小偷到全副武装的抢匪 各种邪恶的蛇头——
from pickpockets to armed robbers,felons of all kinds - -
哈里斯上尉 打扰一下别忘了还有日本忍者
Capt. Harris. Excuse me.Don't forget the gang of ninjas.
我喜欢他们
They're my personal favorites.
干嘛不去找他们玩玩?
Why don't you go pay them a visit?
这一地区需要纪律与组织来掌管
This precinct is run on disciplineand organization.
西蒙说："拉你的左耳朵! "
Simon says, "Pull your left ear."
西蒙说："用你的左脚跳! "加油 伙计们!
Simon says, "Hop on your left foot."Come on, guys.
西蒙说："用你的右脚跳! "
Simon says, "Hop on your right foot."
先生们 这似乎吵了点儿
It's a little too noisy in here, gentlemen.
一会儿有重要的官员检查…
We have importantpolice officials visiting...
我想你们最好表现得乖点
and I think you'd better showthe proper respect.
嘿 中尉 我们马上就好了
Come on, Lieutenant.We're almost finished.
中尉 跟我们一块做西蒙健身操吧!
Come on, Lieutenant,join us in a friendly game of Simon Says.
很简单现在 西蒙说："摸你的脚趾尖! "
There's nothing to it.Now, Simon says, "Touch your toes."
快 中尉 西蒙说："拍你的小手掌! "
Come on, Lieutenant.Simon says, "Clap your hands."
来 一起做!
Come on, get in the spirit.
西蒙说："往左两步走! "
Simon says, "Two steps right."
西蒙说："向后五步走! "
Simon says, "Five steps back."
举起手来!
Put your hands up!
哈哈 西蒙可没那么说!
Simon didn't say.
是的 可史密斯和威森说了
No, but Smith & Wesson does.
高度安全的牢房是用来关押…
The high - security cell areais used to hold criminals...
那些等候审讯的和即将被押送到州、县监狱的犯人的
awaiting trial or transferto state or county facility.
任何已定罪的重犯…
Any convictions involving felons...
性变态者、盗贼等类的犯人被关押在这一区域
perverts, thieves, people of that nature,are held in this area.
- 您能看见这些钢铁结构 - 他到底在这干什么?
- You will notice the steel construction. - What the hell is he doing in there?
我想这样您就明白了吧 长官?
I think that explains it, sir.
快点 快点!
Come on, hurry up!
当和你在一起 一切都有了意义
It's getting to the point nowwhen I'm with you
我不再需要其它任何一样东西
I no longer wantto have something stuck in my eye
你的妈妈 我的妈妈将不再像佛罗伦萨·亨德森
Your mother, my motherain't never looked like Florence Henderson
这是我写给你的
I wrote that for you.
我希望"全民警察"计划的结束…
I hope now that C.O.P. is over...
并不意味着我们再也不会见面
it won't mean that we won'tbe seeing each other anymore.
闭嘴! 没说你 我指的是那些鸭子
Shut up! Not you. I meant the ducks.
注意 这里是费女士
Attention. This is Mrs. F.
- 发生越狱! - 泽得 注意!
- There's been a jailbreak. - Zed, 10 - 4!
塔克 在麦因大街和枫树大街的交汇处接我
Tack, you pick me up at Main and Maple.
快点! 完毕
Move it! Over and out.
校长!
Commandant!
- 发生了越狱 长官 - 上车
- There's been a jailbreak, sir. - Get in.
- 宝贝儿 再见到你可真好 - 被你见到可真好
- It is so wonderful to see you again, baby. - It's wonderful to be seen.
- 就象那些美妙的旧时光 - 在美国 说话没有用
- Just like old times. - ln America, talk is cheap.
越狱了!
There's been a jailbreak!
看 那有一辆被盗的警车 应该就是它
Look, there's a stolen police car.That's got to be it.
我想我们碰到抢劫了
I think we got a robbery in progress.
呆在这儿 费尔德曼女士
Stay here, Mrs. Feldman.
- 不许动! - 说的好
- Freeze! - Good idea.
好 所有人到地下室去!
All right, I want everybodyto get back in that vault.
塔克 给他们做笔录!
Book them, Tack.
- 那是个日本忍者 - 我看见了
- There's a ninja now. - I see him.
走 咱们去抓住他!
Come on, let's get him. Let's go.
看见他了吗?
Do you see him?
噢 可恶
Shit.
好了 如果你们想要打架那么你们就会得到一顿臭揍
All right. If it's a fight you want,a fight you'll get.
混蛋 你要为此付出代价
Damn you. You're gonna pay for that.
闭 嘴!
Shut up!
你们两个笨蛋 给我住嘴!
Will you two morons, knock it off!
我们现在发生的是国际的大事变!
We've got an international incidentgoing on here!
- 我就知道你们会来! - （德）是啊 谢谢!
- I knew you'd come. - Ja, danke.
- 你们应该感谢费尔德曼女士 - 费尔德曼女士是谁?
- You may thank Mrs. Feldman. - Who is Mrs. Feldman?
你们知道费尔德曼女士已经死去了的"全民警察"计划的成员之一
You know Mrs. Feldman,a member of the defunct C.O.P. team.
这里是马霍尼中士 正在追捕一辆被盗的警车
This is Sgt. Mahoneyin pursuit of a stolen police car.
我正驶向威廉姆斯县露天表演场
I'm headed towardsthe Williams County air show.
重复一遍我正向威廉姆斯县方向追捕四名逃犯
Repeat, I'm pursing four escapeestoward the Williams County air show.
现在第二次上场…
Now, folks,making his second appearance...
在威廉姆斯县露天表演场
at the Williams County air show....
- 小心那辆车! - 哪辆车?
- Look out for that car! - What car?
就这辆! 快点 下车!
That car! Come on, get out!
快点!
Come on!
赶紧从这离开!
Let's get out of here!
快点!
Hurry up!
哦 就到这儿了 我可不想上那些东西
This is where I draw the line.I'm not going up in one of those things.
- 不想 绝对不想 - 你可以不去
- No way. No, sirree. - You don't have to.
你现在可以睁开眼睛了
You can open your eyes now.
你怎么会喜欢这个而不喜欢我开车呢?
How can you like thisbetter than my driving?
因为你的车做不了这个!
Because you can't do this in a car.
抢下那气球!
Grab that balloon!
我们以法律的名义征用这气球!
We commandeer this balloonin the name of the law!
- 不 等等 你们不能! - 你们不能这么做! 我们需要它来比赛
- No, wait, you can't! - You can't do that. We need it for the race.
费尔德曼女士 呆在车那儿泽得 斯威特查克 跟我来
Mrs. Feldman, stay with the car.Zed, Sweetchuck, follow me.
伙计们 等等! 塔克贝利!
Guys, wait up! Tackleberry.
- 我该拉什么? - 让它向上!
- What do I pull? - Take it up!
- 它动了! 出发! - 我们在向上升 长官!
- They're getting away! Let's go! - We are going up, sir.
赶快 扔掉降落伞!
Come on! Drop the parachute!
别再瞎闹了!
Stop screwing around!
- 快 扔掉降落伞! - 加油!
- Come on! Drop the parachute! - Come on!
如果他不想这么做 别逼他
If he doesn't want to do it, don't push him.
他只是必须、想自救
He's gotta, like, wanna help himself.
现在让气球降下去!
You land that balloon right now!
我是哈里斯上尉! 你们被捕了!
This is Capt. Harris! You are under arrest!
降落!
Land that balloon now!
- 我在空中将他们击落吧 长官 - 不 还不到时候!
- I'll just blast them out of the sky, sir. - No! Not yet.
您说的对 我应该先鸣枪警告他们一下
You're right.I should give them a warning shot first.
你这个低能儿! 现在高兴了吧?
lmbecile! Are you happy now?
至少看上去我们会降落到河里 长官
At least it looks likewe're coming down in the river.
没关系 因为你会死的!
It won't matterbecause you're going to be dead!
风景真美——
Pretty view - -
我恨水!
I hate water!
救命!
Help!
- 他们掉河里了 - 快点 也许我们能把他们救上来!
- They're in the river. - Hurry. Maybe we can catch them.
我要和塔克贝利并排飞
I'll pull alongside Tackleberry.
瞧 那是我的家!
Look, I see my house!
看 是那帮骗子!
Look, the crooks!
我们去把他们抓住 啊?
Let's go get them, okay?
抓紧了 长官!
Hang on, sir!
- 快点! 别让他们流到瀑布那! - 他们往那边去了!
- Hurry, before they go over the falls! - There they go!
拿绳子!
Get a rope!
坚持住 坚持住 长官!
Hang on. Hang on, sir!
我们马上就来救你们了!
Hang on, we'll come and get you!
抓住它!
Grab it!
别紧张!
Try to relax!
他们在那! 他们跑不掉了
There's the balloon! Now I've got them.
只有一种方法 我去!
There's only one way to do thisand it's up to me!
- 飞到气球上方去! - 他跟你说话呢!
- Take over! - He was talking to you!
带点啤酒回来!
If you're coming back, bring some beer!
- 不 他在跟你说话 - 不不、不 我听见他说了
- No. He was talking to you. - No, I heard him.
- 他说："斯威特查克、斯威特查克飞到气球上方去! " - 不 他没说
- He said, "Sweetchuck, take over." - No, he did not.
- 别踩我的脚! - 闭嘴! 你怎么老没完没了的抱怨?
- Get off of my foot! - Shut up! Why are you always whining?
让我一个人呆着!
Leave me alone!
先生们 请出去你们的许可证!
Gentlemen, may I see your licenseand registration, please?
他们在那儿! 下降!我想近一点儿 再近一点儿
There they are. Take it down.I want to get close. Get closer.
马霍尼 你要干什么?
Mahoney, what are you doing?
离他们再近点儿
Get in closer!
嘿 知道你在干什么吗?
What do you think you're doing?
我来关照关照你 警官!
I'll take care of you, copper!
从机翼上下去! 离开这!
Get off my wing! Get off of there!
你怎么对付他们呢?
What will you do about them?
伙计 结束了 咱们一块回家吧!
Pal, it's over. Let's go home.
- 我恨你 - 我、我才不怕你!
- I hate you. - I'm not really thrilled about you!
- 你干嘛不减减肥? - 你干嘛不到外面走走?
- Why don't you lose some weight? - Why don't you get out and walk?
- 我要吐了! - 我没有降落伞!
- I'm going to be sick! - I don't have a parachute!
- 闭嘴! 我要吐了! - 别弄脏我的衣服!
- Shut up! I'm going to be sick! - Don't be sick on me!
- 我没有降落伞! - 休息会吧!
- I don't have a chute! - Break your fall!
- 掉到小孩们身上! - 不 我要降落伞!
- Hit the kids! - No, I need a chute!
用你自己的! 离我远点!
Get your own! Get away from me!
快点!
Come on!
一块儿掉!
Let go!
我要把你劈成两半 你这个坏蛋!
I'll break you in half, you dweeb.
行了 我打开伞了你满意了吧? 别碰我!
There, I opened the chute.Are you satisfied? Leave me alone!
- 我要杀了你! - 闭上你的嘴享受飞行吧!
- I'm going to kill you! - Shut up and enjoy the flight!
你压着我了!
Get off me!
指挥官 他们说你的"全民警察"成员…
Commandant, they sayyour Citizens On Patrol group...
做了很多很多漂亮的还有疯狂的事情
does many, manywonderful and crazy things.
我认为马霍尼中士应该得到特别的感谢
I think Sgt. Mahoneydeserves a special bow.
- 马霍尼? - 没错!
- Mahoney? - All right!
- 马霍尼? - 哟 出发!
- Mahoney? - Way to go!
起来! 看 是马霍尼!
Get up! Look, it's Mahoney!
- 哪儿? - 噢 我忘了
- Where? - Sorry.
- 为学校干杯 - 干杯
- To the Academy. - To the Academy.
知道吗 你看上去有点象《壮志凌云》里汤姆·克鲁斯
You know, you looka little like Tom Cruise in Top Gun.
- 嗯? - 不!
- Yeah? - No!